<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>
    <string name="temple_of_philae_string">Temple Of Philae</string>
    <string name="pyramids_string">Pyramids</string>
    <string name="temple_of_karnak_string">Temple Of Karnak</string>
    <string name="egyptian_museum_string">Egyptian Museum</string>
    <string name="pyramids_1">The Egyptian pyramids are ancient
        -shaped masonry structures located in Egypt.</string>

    <string name="pyramids_2">The earliest known Egyptian pyramids
        found at Saqqara, northwest of Memphis. The earliest among
        these is the Pyramid of Djoser (constructed 2630 BC–2611 BC)
        which was built during the third dynasty. This pyramid and its
        surrounding complex were designed by the architect Imhotep,
        and are generally considered to be the world is oldest monumental
        structures constructed of dressed masonry. The most famous
        Egyptian pyramids are those found at Giza, on the outskirts of
        Cairo. Several of the Giza pyramids are counted among the largest structures
        ever built. The Pyramid of Khufu at Giza is the largest Egyptian
        pyramid. It is the only one of the Seven Wonders of the Ancient
        World still in existence.</string>

    <string name="pyramids_3">By the time of the Early Dynastic Period,
        those with sufficient means were buried in bench-like
        structures known as mastabas</string>

    <string name="pyramids_4">The second historically-documented
        Egyptian pyramid is attributed to the architect Imhotep,
        who planned what Egyptologists believe to be a tomb for the
        pharaoh Djoser. Imhotep is credited with being the first to
        conceive the notion of stacking mastabas on top of each other,
        creating an edifice composed of a number of "steps" that decreased
        in size towards its apex. The result was the Pyramid of Djoser,
        which was designed to serve as a gigantic stairway by which the
        soul of the deceased pharaoh could ascend to the heavens.
        Such was the importance of Imhotep achievement that he
        was deified by later Egyptians.</string>

    <string name="pyramids_5">The most prolific pyramid-building phase
        coincided with the greatest degree of absolutist rule. It was during
        this time that the most famous pyramids, the Giza pyramid complex,
        were built. Over time, as authority became less centralized, the ability
        and willingness to harness the resources required for construction
        on a massive scale decreased, and later pyramids were smaller, less
        well-built and often hastily constructed.</string>

    <string name="karnak_1">The Karnak Temple Complex, commonly known as Karnak omprises
        a vast mix of decayed temples, chapels, pylons, and other buildings. Construction
        at the complex began during the reign of Senusret I in the Middle Kingdom and continued
        into the Ptolemaic period, although most of the extant buildings date from the New Kingdom.
        The area around Karnak was the ancient Egyptian Ipet-isut ("The Most Selected of Places")
        and the main place of worship of the eighteenth dynasty Theban Triad with the god Amun as its head.
        It is part of the monumental city of Thebes. The Karnak complex gives its name to the
        nearby, and partly surrounded, modern village of El-Karnak, 2.5 kilometres
        (1.6 miles) north of Luxor.</string>

    <string name="karnak_2">he complex is a vast open-air museum, and the second
    argest ancient religious site in the world, after the Angkor Wat Temple of Cambodia.
        It is believed to be the second most visited historical site in Egypt; only the Giza
        Pyramids near Cairo receive more visits. It consists of four main parts, of which only
        the largest is currently open to the general public. The term Karnak often is understood
        as being the Precinct of Amun-Ra only, because this is the only part most visitors see.
        The three other parts, the Precinct of Mut, the Precinct of Montu, and the dismantled Temple
        of Amenhotep IV, are closed to the public. There also
        are a few smaller temples and sanctuaries connecting the Precinct of Mut, the Precinct of
        Amun-Re, and the Luxor Temple.</string>

    <string name="karnak_3">The Precinct of Mut is very ancient, being dedicated to an Earth and
        creation deity, but not yet restored. The original temple was destroyed and partially restored
        by Hatshepsut, although another pharaoh built around it in order to change the focus or
        orientation of the sacred area. Many portions of it may have been carried away for use in other buildings.</string>

    <string name="egyptian_museum_1">The Museum of Egyptian Antiquities, known commonly as the Egyptian Museum or Museum of Cairo
        , in Cairo, Egypt, is home to an extensive collection of ancient Egyptian antiquities.
        It has 120,000 items, with a representative amount on display, the remainder in storerooms.
        The edifice is one of the largest museums in the region. As of July 2017, the museum is open to the public.</string>

    <string name="egyptian_museum_2">he Egyptian Museum of Antiquities contains many important
        pieces of ancient Egyptian history. It houses the world’s largest collection of Pharaonic
        antiquities. The Egyptian government established the museum built in 1835 near the Ezbekeyah
        Garden and later moved to the Cairo Citadel. In 1855, Archduke Maximilian of Austria was given
        all of the artifacts
        by the Egyptian government; these are now in the Kunsthistorisches Museum, Vienna.</string>

    <string name="egyptian_museum_3">
        There are two main floors in the museum, the ground floor and the first floor.
        On the ground floor there is an extensive collection of papyrus and coins used
        in the Ancient world. The numerous pieces of papyrus are generally small fragments,
        due to their decay over the past two millennia. Several languages are found on these pieces,
        including Greek, Latin, Arabic, and ancient Egyptian. The coins found on this floor are made
        of many different metals, including gold, silver, and bronze. The coins are not only Egyptian,
        but also Greek, Roman, and Islamic. This has helped historians research the history of Ancient Egyptian trade.
        Also on the ground floor are artifacts from the New Kingdom, the time period between 1550 and 1069 BC.
        These artifacts are generally larger than items created in earlier centuries. Those items include statues,
        tables, and coffins (sarcophagi), it also contains 42 rooms, upon entering through the security check in the
        building, one looks toward the atrium and the rear of the building with many items on view from sarcophagi and boats to enormous statues.
        On the first floor there are artifacts from the final two dynasties of Egypt, including items from the tombs of
        he Pharaohs Thutmosis III, Thutmosis IV, Amenophis II, Hatshepsut, and the courtier Maiherpri, as well as
        many artifacts from the Valley of the Kings, in particular the material from the intact tombs of Tutankhamun
        and Psusennes I. Two special rooms contain a number of mummies of kings and other royal family members of the
        New Kingdom.
    </string>

    <string name="philae_1">Philae  is currently an island in the reservoir of the Aswan Low Dam downstream
        of the Aswan Dam and Lake Nasser, Egypt. Philae was originally located near the expansive First Cataract
        of the Nile in Upper Egypt and was the site of an Egyptian temple complex. These rapids and the
        surrounding area have been variously flooded since the initial construction of the Aswan Low Dam in 1902.
        The temple complex was later dismantled and relocated to nearby Agilkia Island as part of the UNESCO Nubia
        Campaign project,
        protecting this and other complexes before the 1970 completion of the Aswan High Dam</string>

    <string name="philae_2">Philae is mentioned by numerous ancient writers,
        including Strabo, Diodorus Siculus, Ptolemy, Seneca,
        Pliny the Elder. It was, as the plural name indicates,
        the appellation of two small islands situated in latitude 24° north
        , just above the First Cataract near Aswan (Egyptian Swenet "Trade;" Ancient Greek: Συήνη).
        Groskurd computes the distance between these islands and Aswan at about 100 km (62 mi).</string>

    <string name="philae_3">Despite being the smaller island, Philae proper was,
        from the numerous and picturesque ruins formerly there, the more interesting of the two.
        Prior to the inundation, it was not more than 380 metres (1,250 ft) long and about 120 metres
        (390 ft) broad. It is composed of syenite:
        its sides are steep and on their summits a lofty wall was built encompassing the island.</string>

</resources>
